Thank you for watching!
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
I'm Emi Kawasami, your host today.
Bon appétit!
This is the 195th Ukka no banquet de Fukuna showroom.
This time, I would like to deliver a subtitle for this show.
We're going to decide on the subtitle with Yuzo until now.
and then we'll deliver a program based on the subtitle.
It's an original rule of Ukka!
Yes, I'll do it.
That's right.
This time, too.
The title.
Subtitle?
I'd like to decide.
I don't have a specific one in mind.
That's for sure.
Well...
This week, or rather, this showroom...
I think this week's showroom will be mainly free talk.
That's right.
Don't get carried away.
Please send us anything and everything.
Whatever you think.
That's right.
It's hot.
It's the 10th anniversary of the showroom?
Oh, wow.
There's something in here.
Congratulations! Congratulations!
Oh, my God.
There's a box outside. Oh, my God.
I wonder what we'll do with it.
A free talk session. On the contrary.
I say anything is fine, but it's hard. It's hard. It's the hardest thing I've ever heard.
I want to tell everyone that anything is fine, anything is fine.
I wonder if anything would be good... I wonder if anything would be good...
I don't know if anything's okay...
I'll just say good evening.
Good evening.
Good evening" is the subtitle for this year's event.
I didn't expect that title.
I'm going to call the title.
Yuka no Yukari Dizner Showroom Good evening.
Good evening.
I'm Yuka.
Scam Genuine
Scam real
You chewed so hard.
What language is this?
As I said before, today's newlywed is Kansai Yume, please.
Heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart
And...
I'm Ruri Aoi.
I want, I want, I want...
I am Yuukirina, please take care of me.
No way! Triangle! No way, triangle.
Thank you for playing the 195th Yukari Dizner Showroom today!
Thank you very much.
And now, it's time to spread the word.
Let's spread the word!
In order for as many people as possible to see this broadcast, I'm going to post a notice on Entos now, so please spread the word.
Please spread the word.
How about a "Good evening" today?
Good evening.
Good evening to you too.
That's right.
Greetings are important.
It's the most important thing.
Let's say good evening.
Okay.
I'll wait for "Good evening.
Waiting for "Good evening.
It's pretty cool.
Here they come.
Here you go.
How's it going? Is it good?
Is it good?
Yes. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Good evening, Mr. Pose.
We're going to be tweeting a lot of announcements on Twitter right now.
I'll be tweeting a lot of announcements.
So please, everyone, repost this.
Is this a repost?Is this a repost?
I don't know.
I tried.
Repost mark
Please repost!
So, since the last showroom...
There have been quite a few events since the last showroom.
I'm going to announce them one by one.
Today, November 8th.
Rising Dream, a new song by Ukka, has been distributed in advance!
Yay!
On the 8th, on the 8th...
We are going to release our first full album on December 20th.
We'll be releasing our first full-length album on December 20th, and one of the songs from the album has been pre-distributed.
Have you listened to it?
Of course I have.
I also listened to it this morning while doing my mate.
Oh, well...
I played it or something.
I did?
Yes, I did.
I did, didn't I?
The new song.
I love it so much!
I'm so happy.
I've been playing it for a long time.
I played it so many times.
I put it on repeat a little bit in the morning and went to work.
So that's what I'm talking about, folks. That's what I'm talking about, gentlemen.
Oh, man.
Listen to this.
This... is the most important dream.
I love it. I love it. I love it.
It's refreshing.
I love it.
Something's coming.
It's so soft.
It's like this.
It's nice. It's nice. This is great.
I've only sent you the first number here, but I think it will be the background music from here on,
I think it will be background music from here on,
If you want to listen to it more often, you can subscribe now,
If you want to listen to it more often, it is available on the subscriber's site now, so please do. Please take a look.
Please take a look.
Do you have a favorite part?
My favorite part is my part,
I really like the first part of the second verse, including the choreography.
Everyone is like this.
Like a train.
Like this. You're looking at me a lot, Ruri.
She watches me a lot, too.
I'm rooting for you, Ruri.
I'm rooting for you.
I'm rooting for you,
I'm going to send her off. I'll see her off.
That's good, that's good.
I'm sure everyone will be here to see you take it,
So, you'll be in soon. Thank you. I know you're rooting for me. Be that way soon. Thanks. I know you're rooting for me.
I performed at the staff, at the time of the staff.
It was so good then.
But I was terrible.
How are you doing?
I forgot,
I'll have a cup of Iwamori's,
Oh, that's right! What's up with everyone?
It's like this.
Everyone was thinking about her so hard,
I was thinking of Ruri, so I thought..,
I thought it was Ruri,
So I was a bit withdrawn.
Yes, I tend to pull back.
I forgot about that.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I've had my hands full these days.
Do you have a favorite place, Rina-chan? A favorite place.
I wonder.
I like this part. It's my part during the chorus,
West, westward, like this.
Like this, like this.
I really like it. I really like it.
I'm particular about it.
I like the way I sing,
I like it. It worked out well.
I don't know if this happens every time,
I think the soundtrack and the live performance are quite different,
The soundtrack is beautifully done, but the live performance is not, The soundtrack is beautifully done, but when it comes to the live performance, it's a bit difficult for everyone to understand,
But in a live performance, you can see the feelings of the audience,
But when it comes to the live performance, it's a little bit more involved, you know, like the feelings of the audience,
Yes, that's right.
So it sounds a little different,
I think it sounds a little different in live performance,
I would like you to see it in a live performance,
I would like you to see it at the live performance.
Yes.
This time, I would like you to see this dance,
Kana-sensei, who is always in my lessons,
Kana-sensei.
Kana-sensei, in the past, well, Believe,
First love,
Mowamowamowa,
KIRALIPSU,
etc,
and so on,
I had them choreograph for me,
This time, too,
I always feel like a member of the group,
We had a lot of fun,
We had a lot of fun choreographing.
It was really fun.
Ena-chan, you know Kana-sensei's quirks,
You know Kana-sensei's quirks, don't you?
Yes, I know.
I found it,
The usual is to do this kind of thing for free,
Ena-chan, raise your right hand, Ena-chan, raise your right hand,
Next, raise your left hand,
And I manage to do it,
and then, at the end,
Then,
What to do,
I'm going to do something,
They repeat it one more time, that kind of thing.
Oh, yeah, the things to do, you know.
You're going to teach me.
Summarize what I just said,
What to do,
The things to do,
And say,
I've been thinking about that for a long time, and I've been thinking about that for a long time,
I've been thinking about that for a long time,
From the beginning, actually,
From the beginning?
From your side,
We've been working on it together,
Since the beginning,
You've been doing this for quite a long time, haven't you?
That's right.
And then..,
I finally told him,
Yes, I did,
The other day, too,
I'll do what I have to do,
I'm sure he'll be able to see me,I was definitely getting facial recognition,
I was aware of it.
I think the teacher was aware of it,
You are aware of it now, aren't you?
You are aware of it, aren't you?
That's right.
Yes, why is that?
The choreography is pretty good, too,
It's easy for everyone to imitate,
The choruses, for example,
The chorus, for example, is easy for everyone to imitate, and the theme is easy to match,
It gives a sense of luxury,
We also made a little effort on TikTok this time,
That's right.
We are doing it,
I have my own TikTok,
Every day,
I think it is probably the best way to
I think,
Soon,
I don't know,
I really don't know,
Is there a TikTok on the relieve?
Surely,
It's possible.
Will there be filming?
I don't know,
I hope everyone will learn the choreography,
I'd like to ask you all to learn the choreography.
Let's do it together,Together,
We will be waiting for you.
Please wait for us.
With everyone,
I'll be waiting for your response.
I think I can dance,
But you know what?
We'll dance.
Let's see the train off together.
Don't look there.
You're not seeing me off, are you?
Yes.
And, you know..,
December 20th.
The first full-length album of a major label,
The title,
It's been decided.
Yay!
We are looking forward to it.
Let me tell you what happened,
A coming-of-age novel,
Music journal lecture.
I've got it.
It's wonderful.
I don't know, it's like this,
I would say that it drags on the coming-of-age novel,
Yes, it is.
I would say that it drags on a coming-of-age novel,
A theme.
Yes.Yes.
In,
It's called a coming-of-age novel,
And the subtitle of the novel is something like,
Music Ki Kou this time.
About the album,
Yes.
And the jacket design of this album,
jacket design for the album has also been released.
I would like to invite you all to take a look at it.
I'm very curious about it.
Various things.
This is it,
Please send off the train.
Look away from the train.
All of you.
Send off the train.
Thank you for waiting.
Hello.
Well, I'm sure we'll get to it eventually,
I think it's a question you'll want to incorporate,
Various.
Send this to the train.
Ha-ha-ha.
Send it to the train.
Take me to the train.
You're sending it to the train, aren't you?
I mean, we don't have any of this stuff, right?I mean, we don't have the materials for this, do we?
Yes, we do.
We don't have this.
Is that Twitter?
I'll have to look for it.
And official LINE?
Yes, yes, yes.
They sent it to me.
You sent it, didn't you?
No, it's this one.
You're right.
She's looking out the door when it's open.
That's right.
I see.
Momochan, you're the only one facing forward.
Isn't she looking this way?
No, she's just barely looking right.
Really?
Yes, I'm sure.
That's right.
Your body's facing this way.
Oh, really?
That's amazing.
High definition.
It's too high quality.
I don't know. They all had ponytails, right?
That's right.
I guess it's the image of girls who go on a trip and tie their hair up in a single strand
to get into the spirit of the trip.
That's why the team decided to use a ponytail.The Neo team...
Right.
So everyone's in ponytails.
Yeah. - Yeah.
How'd it go?
Yeah, it was good.
You look so cute with your flexed legs, Ruri.
I'm embarrassed.
Oh, no.
I can see a little.
She's sitting up straight, too.
She's got Rina-chan's face.
It's a stool, a stool, a stool.
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Are you uploading it?
Please don't upload it.
Excuse me, bottom left.
Definitely not up.
Why don't you put it up?
It's not here at all.
But listen to this.
The eyeliner?
You put on some kind of green... eyeliner.
Green.
I put on an inordinate amount of it.
I put it on.
So you bought it.
It was like, "Don't worry, it's still good.
I know.
You've got my back. I'm so glad I got your support.
They told me to go further.
I said, "That green," and when I saw the finished product...
It's not the same face.
It's like he's trying to be nice to me.
Isn't the face just different?
Yeah...
That's for sure.
I've already said that.
Yeah.
They don't always go well together.
I've been told it's not a good fit.
You're not doing great, but you don't fit in.
You're not doing well, Yona-chan.
Oh, man...
I'm not going to do what you just said.
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I can't do it.
But... the jacket looks great.
And there's a little bit of green in it.
So please pick it up when it comes out and take a good look at it.
Take a good look at Nena-chan.
Don't just look at me.
I'll make sure you take a good look at it.
Oh no!
I can see it.
Yes, sir.
And... on October 29th, there was an after-prize festival. Yes, and yes, there was an after-prize festival on October 29th!
That's right!
At Yoko Ann!
Yay!
Yes!
More than a week ago?
That's right.
Almost a week.
That's fast.
That fast?
Already.
Did everyone see it?
I know some of you were there, but we also streamed it.
I think you could see us until the 5th.
We also performed the Rising Navi for the first time.
Yes, we did.
We also performed Everybody Wannabe, the last chorus of which was performed on the sub-stage.
We danced on the sub-stage for 85 minutes.
And we danced.
It was fun!
I had a good time
That was fun.
I got a "yes"!
Just a little.
Really...
I...
I really...The
Wanabee's
e what?
WANNABE
B
Also known as B
B's when they go to the main stage or the sub-stage.
Ayamachan was so cool!
I'm serious.
At that time, I was a little...
What was it?
We were on the "Rain Cargo".
We went on the Soul of Rain.
Oh, I went.
I thought that was nice.
My bangs didn't fall out.
You're a pro!
He's running like that now.
It's fixed.
That's amazing.
It'd be fun to wear that.
The point of interest is the bangs.
It's not a running part.
No matter how far you run, the bangs will stay in place.
That's why I said I'd split it horizontally.
That's right.Yes, I know.
It's the first time.
I'm more emotional than usual.
Did you feel that?
When I looked back.
I was looking at the archives.
Oh, so there's a lot more in there than usual.
Yeah.
It's a side split, so it's more thoughtful.
Yeah, I guess so.
I mean, the MC after the show.
It's a live show with Nekobo.
With Mea...
And the day before rehearsal...
The other groups...
We rehearsed in the gymnasium.
Even in the gymnasium, I could see the side split
So...
Even if we did it as a one-man show
I could see that it would be a success.
I could see that it was going to be a success.
So we'll do it, too.
I'm a one-man operation.
In a big place.
So for the show...
We're going to do the side split.
I want to show that I can do it as a one-man show.
I want to show that I can do it.
I want to see us do yokowari.
I want to see us doing yokowari. I want to show you how I do it.
I wanted to show you.
I wanted to show you how I do it.
I really got into it.
And the most important thing was that it was a lot of fun.
That's right.
It was fun, wasn't it?
If you show a big side split, you can't lose.
At our time.
That's right.
If they don't think it's a good fit...
After all, you can't see the side view.
I'll show it to them.
That's right.
I was very conscious of my hands.
I might have been emotional.
Like, "I don't understand!
You're making a lot of noise.
No, it was great.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Let's try it again.
Try it again.
Jun-chan!
Too Jun-chan!
Please stop using the Jun-chan terminology!
Please stop using "Jun-chan"!
It was fun, wasn't it?
Yeah, it was.
For those of you who don't know about Ukka... You all and anyone else who doesn't know about Ukka.
like you enjoyed it.
I could really feel it.
In the medley, you know, the candy floss pants.
So...
So, the question is...
The birth of the problem.
It was perfect, wasn't it?
From the beginning to the end.
Before the very fast-talking part.
I was on the mainstage side of the aisle, and I had to dash to get there in time.
You had to dash to get there in time.
It was amazing.
I was laughing so hard.
I was laughing so hard into the mic at that point.
Laugh!
I was like, "Oh, my voice is being said too.
It was so funny.
That's why I failed.
Oh, yeah.
I'm sorry.
My voice...
I didn't say it didn't work.
It's just... it was so much fun.
I didn't say it... and then I ran.
It was a lost cause.
It was fun.
I was like, "Yay!
Yay! Yay!
LOL!
I cheated.
It's a bright house, isn't it?
I'm having fun, aren't I?
Hey.
The last song.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I had to do it.
Before we knew we were going to do it...
We had a fixed lesson date, right?
Yes, yes, yes
And I was...
I had something to do
Yes, yes, I thought...
Kashiwari was handed out to everyone.
And you found out about it later.
I was confident that Rina would spoil it for me.
I was confident.
She was very confident.
So there were many, many pictures.
Like, "Ayamu, you saw the last one.
No, she hasn't seen it yet.
It's like right after you got here.
Maybe she did.
I don't think so.
What? What what what what? I said, "What's going on?
I went to the answer.
It says "Kawase.
It's like, "That's great. Like, "That's great!
Ayamu, you are the center of this, for sure!
I got so excited.
Isn't she the one who wants to say it quickly?
When I looked at it, I saw my part of the page.
I was thinking, "I'm going to dance with Amihola.
I was watching LulliaTalk's performance.
I wondered what Ami-chan was doing.
I opened the answer.
Do you want to answer? I showed her that we were all going to do it together.
I showed it to her and she said, "YOU ARE THE.
I showed it to her, and she said, "YOU ARE THE.
I don't know what YOU ARE THE.
And then the CFD answer is YOU ARE THE.
And then, where the name is written...
I saw "Kawase".
Was there a "Kawase" in Momokura?
No, there isn't.
Of course not.
So do Ayame.
That's when things got exciting.
I told Momoa-chan first.
Oh, you told Momoko.
I told Momoa-chan to do Ayame-chan.
But Ayame's not here.
I couldn't tell her how happy I was.
He's here.
Now or never!
Ayame-chan said, "I've got this.Ayame-chan said this!
YOU ARE THE" definitely means Ayame-chan!
Oh, I thought that's what you meant.
I was on a roll.
Ayame-chan, I'm already impressed.
I was so bored.
Ohisari, that was amazing.
I thought, "Ayame-chan.
I thought so.
I was so happy.
I was happy too.
But... you guys are amazing.
An-chan, you're really cute.
They said a lot of things like, "You're so cute!
I'm so glad I did it.
I'm so happy!
Thank you very much for the Staffurafest!
Thank you very much!
Yes, and the 31st of October was also a bad day, wasn't it?
It was a day of rage!
A day of rage
It was a day of rage
On the 31st, you know
We were able to put on Halloween Land in Nana Land!
Thank you very much
Thank you very much!
In Shibuya on Halloween day
Yes.
And...
We also decided to dress upWe decided to dress up too.
Yes, sir.
What did we dress up as?
Yes...
We dressed up as the Cherry Blossom Chinese.
Oh!
It's already past the diagonal.
It's way up.
I was like, "What's going on?
But it was the first time for me to wear the "Sakura Innies" costume.
It was my first time.
The new Carvel and...
Umu-maru-maru-shii costume.
Marumaru Shi...
Marumaru shi
It's a Marumaru-shii costume!
Mm-hmm.
DOMARUSHI-KA
DOMARUSHI-
How did you like it?
Well, I'd never worn it before, so it was new.
You didn't know...
I didn't know it was called that.
I heard you've never worn it before.
That's right, that's right.
It's like, "Is it okay if I do it the other way around?
It's fine.
On the contrary.
I was really happy to hear that, even though I didn't know if it was a good idea.
Really? Oh, really?
I'm so happy, I'm so happy, I'm so happy.
I think it's good.
I already saw it in the jacket picture.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
I was wondering if it would fit in with what I've been hearing lately.
Oh, no, it's true.
It's not that... it's just... it's from when you were a little girl.
When you were little.
I was a little girl, so I thought it might be okay.
Yes, yes, yes.
And then there was the fitting day.
And I said, "Are you sure you're okay?" And it just fell right into place.
You want to go in? Like that.
I'm the one who's screwed up.
I'm no longer...
No longer.
I don't know if I can wear this in my own clothes now.
What?
I was like, "What?" and then I was like, "Oh, my God.
I'm so glad I fit in.
I'm so glad it fits.
I'm glad I could wear it.
Well, maybe you've seen this outfit on Sakura Ebbets, but this is the first time you've seen them in it.
But I think this is the first time I've seen the two of you in it.
I thought it was really rare.
I also wore the past costumes for my birthday photo...
Yes.
I didn't want to wear it. I didn't want to get covered in it.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
That's how I found out about Amedakji.
Yeah. - Yeah.
And the scrolls were so perfect with this one of mine.
It was my favorite outfit.
Yeah. - Yeah.
In the Sakura Evies.
Lucky.
Oh, my God.
That's amazing.
It was so cute.
I wish I could have worn that one.
I loved that one, too.
Actually, it's just this one.
Just this one.
I had my favorites, too.
That one... that was my favorite one, too.
It was a tricolore.
It's a talker, isn't it?
That was so good.
Twinkle, twinkle, twinkle.
Sparkles? Sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle...
Table color.
That Moa-chan's...
Oh, the men's one.
I really like that Bompi, including the colors.
What? But it's cute, isn't it?
I liked it and wanted to wear it.
I thought I wanted to wear it, but then I realized that not many people were wearing it. I don't know, people didn't wake up too much.
What? That's right.
Right? Like that.
Oh, seriously.
I didn't say it before, but I actually loved it.
Oh, yeah.
I'm sorry.
Okay, so next time, you're going to love it, too.
What? My favorite too.
Good luck with that.
It's official.
Sure thing.
No, please give it to me.
Yes, so definitely
Definitely give it over, please.
Absolutely.
Why, you know... I think you guys could see us...
I think they saw us.
I think it's the first and last time.
Sakura Ebbies.
I'm going to live my impression.
It was Halloween, so we could do it.
Yeah, I know.
I heard something about that.
Oh, so?
It's what we did.
So... everyone...
Thank you for Halloween in Shibuya
Thank you very much.
And the 4th of November... Yes, and it was the 4th of November.
I, Kawanishi Motomura, a director of Hoshi Board of Directors, was a birthday flow live!
Thank you for your hard work
Thank you very much.
Well, the first part was the director's birthday.
The second part was my birthday.
Rina-chan!
Rina-chan was in a mix-up, so she didn't get a chance to see the show.
Mi-chan came to see the event.
Yes, I went.
How was it?
Riju got a response first.
I see.
We had a time for shooting.
I tried my best to maximize the number of kisses.
I gave her a kiss, and she returned it.
I thought it was a response to me.
I mounted a guy who was nearby, thinking he was responding to me.
Riju-chan is not so much a cute Riju-chan, but a cool, mature, cool Riju-chan.
Riju-chan is more of a cool, mature, cool girl.
It was refreshing to see her singing in a mature and cool way, rather than as a cute little girl.
It was refreshing to see her singing.
It suited her so well.
Rižu was so cute.
We only saw each other in the white ones.
I thought it was so cute.
They looked good together, didn't they?
The first outfit looked like aurora borealis.
I saw it for the first time that day.
The mazuki one?The mazuki one?
Yes, yes.
It was cute, like Rapunzel.
But not like Rijiu?
Like Aurora Borealis.
Very Riji-chan!
The hair on the camera was also very Riji-esque.
It was cute.
After that, wasn't it unexpected?
Shia's.
Dancing...
You did more of the dance stuff.
It was cool.
It was great.
I felt like I saw so many different Riju-chan.
It was sparkling.
Masaki's stuff was so sparkly!
The stage bye was amazing, wasn't it?
It was like this.
Riju was so cool!
I'll be glad to see him.
It's coming through.
It's going to reach him.
It's coming.
Oh, please.
You seemed to be in different spirits than you've ever been at a show before.
Yes, it was
That was good.
Is it nice, Liju?
Liv, it's Ambi. Liv is an Ambi, sir.
Yes, it is.
What do you want to do this time?
First of all, let's start with him.
First of all.
I'd like to ask you a favor.
Yes, that's right.
But the theme of this year's event is to look back on the birthdays up to now.
Since this is the last birthday live, I've tried to put all the things I wanted to do in the live.
The first song was "Eternal Trinity".
It was so hard!
It was really frustrating.
Do it!
I've wanted to sing this song for a long time, so I thought it would be a surprise if I sang it as the first song at this timing.
I'm sure everyone will be astonished.
So we did it, and then we did a block of songs we've sung at past birthdays, and then we did a block of songs we've sung at past birthdays.
But this block was the toughest.
I can't say.
I can't say it.
I can't tell you how tight it was.
It's really high, isn't it?
It's so high!
I made it to one half, but everyone was having so much fun that they jumped and stuff.
Everyone helped me a lot.
Thank you!
And then there's Tsui.
Oh, it's Nichiyo!
Yes, yes, yes.
Nichiyo's skill-split version is the standard birthright version The skill-splitting version of Nichiyo is the standard birthright version.
Yes.
This is the third or third time this year.
This is the version of Nichiyo in which she repeats her favorite part, the skill division, three times.
Yes.
And then we play some old songs in a cute block...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then we finished with this song, and then the encore... the encore was so great, it was like a book...
Yes.
And then we did the encore, which was just as good as the original, but we did a couple of songs and then Eddie Buddy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We'll end with "Love Parade," which I'm sure you'll all enjoy.
I love it!
Love Parade is the B-melody I've been longing for!
I know, I've been saying that for a long time.
I've been wanting to get out so badly.
I've been saying that I love you so much.
I've been wanting to get out there for so long.
And now I've finally done it!
We finally got to do it.
How was it, Ruru-chan?
I was really impressed by the Love Parade.
Yes, yes...
You said you wanted to sing it last year.
Yeah, yeah, yeah...
But the Love Parade was too cool.
Oh, really...
There's that part in the chorus where she's making her usual decisions.
You were passing by
Oh, my God, Suki party! Oh, my God, this is my Suki party.
Like it?
Like Party
I like that party.
Wait a minute.
I've never heard of a skipper party.
You mean a "Skipper" party?
Suki party
Skipper is that thing...
That's right.
I didn't know that.
Well, no, no, no...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Don't worry about it.
Ta-da, ta-da, ta-da, ta-da, ta-da, ta-da...
Ta-da! Ta-da!
No, no, no, no.
It's different.
What's with the face?
What are you trying to say?
I usually dance while doing it, so I can't really ask.
From the outside.
That's right.
It was a lot of fun to listen to you this time.
And as for Ayumi's mount, her earrings...
During the encore...
The earrings I was wearing were the earrings I gave you for your birthday.
And this one too.
This one, too. It's this one.
It's cute.
I was wondering if it was the main item.
It's the main item.
It's so cute!
Yu-chan gave it to me as a birthday present on the day of the rehearsal for my birthday.
So I got it then and decided to wear it for the encore.
I was so happy that she was able to wear it.
I don't know if I was able to wear it, but I was wearing a T-shirt, skirt and loafalo for the encore.
I don't know if I was able to wear it, but I was wearing a T-shirt, a skirt and a loafalo.
I was wearing it for the 2021
I wore it for my birthday in 2021.
It was your first birthday, wasn't it?
That's right.
I remember.
You wore it, right?
Yes, I did.
I brought Tovida's skirt and loafers.
I don't know if you noticed, because no one mentioned it.
I don't know if you noticed, but I felt a little bit of the birth of the past there, too.
I don't know if anyone was there.
I don't know if there was anyone who didn't have it.
Please, please, please, please.
Put it on.
I see.
I didn't know.
I see. You didn't know?
That's right.
I also displayed the albums that everyone had given me in the past in the back of the room. I also had some albums that people had given me in the past displayed in the back of the room.
I think there was a banner as you entered the venue.
I think there was a banner when you entered the venue, but it was also decorated with things that fans had given to me in the past.
The mannequins were wearing the birthday items that were given to them by the fans in the past and they could feel the past birthdays.
It was really fun.
It was great!
I entered the venue and was about to go to Rik-chan's place, but it was right next to me.
There it was!
Scary, scary!
He was so fast.
He just let me go.
I was scared.
It wasn't me.
It was a fake.
Ha-ha-ha.
It's really crystal.
I know, right?
I included a lot of crystals.
It was really good!
Thank you everyone, and thank you, Rik-chan!
Thank you very much.
And the next day, November 5th, was the Relieve Omiya!
Oh!
That's a recent memory.
Yes, it was.
That was the day of Sapporo.
It was the first time for me to go to Sapporo for this releive.
It was my first time in Sapporo, and it was the first time for me to be in Sapporo.
You took a lot of beautiful pictures of me.
Yes, yes, yes. Mm-hm-hm.
And I saw the video.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Thank you so much for everything.
You look beautiful.
It was beautiful.
I'm so happy for you.
Yeah, yeah.
And there's still a lot more to come.
I'm sure we'll see you again.
I don't know, maybe... maybe we'll see you again sometime.
That's right.
When we have more songs?
That's for sure.
I think it will be a challenge.
Yeah, yeah.
I hope you're looking forward to it.
I'll be looking forward to it.
It's over.
But we're right on schedule.
I'm going to the corner.
Yes, we are.
Pintarie.
Yes.
eh?
Oh...Oh!
arm cramps
Oh, man.
Oh, no!
This is really bad!
Oh, my God.
Now that I've seen it, it fits like a glove.
Oh, my God!
Pazzdority!
I have to tell you.
I don't know if she'll notice, so you'd better tell her.
I'd like to go to the corner now.
Okay.
The subtitle was "Good evening," right?
Good evening.
I wonder if it's a "good evening" type of thing.
Let's have a good evening.
Yay!
What's that?
What's this?
We'll choose a situation and each say good evening. Vote for the best good evening.
You already gave up being in there.
Good evening.
That's funny.
The first theme.
What?
There's a theme. There's a theme to it.
Good evening at the MC after singing 3 songs at the opening of the Tokyo Dome concert.
We performed three songs at the Tokyo Dome concert... three opening songs and then good evening everyone.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's quite an important conversation.
It's true that you've got the spirit of the show.
That's right.
I have to imagine Tokyo Dome once.
It's huge.
It's pretty big.
Can I put "everyone" on it?
I'll leave it to you.
Who'll go first?
I'll go first, since I usually say "Good evening" when I MC.
Good evening, Master.
It's easy to imagine... the Tokyo Dome.
Of course.
Thank you very much.
Good evening, everyone.
But, but, but...
The sixth time was OK.
Yes, it's true.
The volume of the Tokyo Dome is the only thing that's loud.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's like, "Good evening, everyone.
"Good evening, everyone.
I want it to go all the way to the back.
It's important important
That's important.
That's good.
You see this?
I thought it was a dome.
What a surprise.
It's not a studio.
Okay, I'll go.
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
Yes, indeed.
Good evening.
Like left, right and center.
I can extend my voice.
Good evening.
Like this.
That's me.
Yes, like this.
Okay, Rina-chan.
Rina-chan.
Tokyo dam, please.
Good evening, everyone!
This is terrible. What's the last one?
Good evening!
Oh, I mean Sei. Sei, good evening.
I'm sure everyone will answer if I say so.
That's true.
If it was just one person...
But this is something to think about.This, you know, is something to think about.
Yes, it is, isn't it?
What kind of currency?
I'm sure.
What currency does that sound like to you?
Thank you very much.
That's funny.
So, this theme is from the Tokyo Dam concert.
I wonder if this is the first word of good evening in the MC after the opening three songs.
Yes, sir.
Tokyo Dam performance
Each backstage is different.
What should we do?
What should I do?
What should I do for the first song?
Hanhwaul. I like Hanhwaul so much.
I want to chew on Hanhwaul.
Hanhwaul.
So...
This is so hard...
It's gonna take a long time.
One chance
What's that?
But the third song should be like, "Glow Up" or something...
And then we'll end it cool, like this.
And then you all go like, "Koumaha...
I see.
I want to do it in a cool way. I want to go for a cool look.
I want to be cool.
I like that one for the third song, T-SPIRIT
Yes, yes, yes!
I want to be like "wow"!
Yes, yes, yes...
Ria-chan?
What's the third song?
I'm sure it's "Ho kara riru" or something like that, right? star girl designs devoted to star girl
Sound good?
I'm looking forward to the Tokyo Dome show!
Japanese people today.
I can see it.
I didn't expect to see you here.
I saw all this.
It's a big deal.
I'm going to the Tokyo Dome.
Are you ready?
Okay, thank you very much for your vote.
All right.
Let's do it.
Let's see how you do.
Number 3, Kina.
That's great.
Thank you.
So cute.
Yes, it is.
It's important.
Encore performance
Encore performanceEncore Performance
Good evening
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
Who's that?
It's not Yume, it's Ari.
Doesn't she sound like an ant?
I think there might be ants around here somewhere.
Are there ants around here?
That's funny.
Okay, let's move on to the second one.
There's one... when you meet your missing loved one for the first time in 30 years... and you say, "Good evening.
That's not easy.
Missing loved one.
Not good... after 30 years...
What's inside?
Maybe he's filming.
It's like an acting lesson.
It's possible that they met by chance at the same moment they met.
It could be a cash register at a convenience store. What do you mean, the magazine went missing in mid-series?
I mean, he's doing update 2, and then he disappears.
I think that was it...
I think that was it.
It's a good idea because it's an eye-catcher.
I'm not sure why you're inos
Okay
I know, I know.
I know, I know, I know, I know, I'm meeting someone, but it's 8 o'clock, hurry up!
I'll wait for you... and if you're 5 minutes late, I'll let you off the hook.
Good evening.Good evening.
Eh, I wonder.
If I say "eh," it's like...
I said, "Good evening.
It's like you didn't understand me.
I said good evening this time of night.
It's 34 o'clock.
5 o'clock.
Good evening? Like that.
I'm sure it's there.
You'd think someone who looks like you would.
30 years.
Thirty years.
It's been 1993.
If it were true, I wouldn't have been born.
That's the level we're at now.
Become 2025.
Eh, live, eh,
You just appeared right in front of me?
I mean, this...
It's you, isn't it?
Good evening.
I can't believe it.
I can't believe it's time.
I don't know where this is coming from.
It's not like that.
It's hard to tell.
Okay, I'll go.
Okay.
We had a good time today, didn't we? Hey, I had a good time today, didn't I?
Good evening.
I'll laugh.
I'm serious.
I'm on a date with someone new, and we're talking about how much fun we had.
And he's walking around with some girl he doesn't know.
I see.
When I heard that...
Did they come?
Did you see many of them?
Did he call you by your name?
Who?
Satoshi.
Satoshi, he said you had a good time today.
That way?
Satoshi, come here.
Like Takahashi.
Takahashi.
Hey...
There's a singer here.
Three singers.
It's difficult, difficult, indeed, but as a performer, I'm in a lot of trouble.
You're right. So, what about Ruri-chan's Takashi?
Is it a lover's trick? Or a 30-year-old Takashi?
30 years ago Takashi. 30 years ago Takashi.
He's still Takashi... he's time-selling.
He's definitely still Takashi, 30 years ago.
Wait a minute. What are you doing?
I'm just shopping. Is it just a coincidence or is it normal? It's like I'm shopping.
I'm going shopping.
Good evening. Good evening.
Good evening.
I just want to talk about what I'm taking with me.
something like that.
I just wanted a place to start.
Yeah, I know.
But you didn't really mean good evening?
Of course not.
When I'm finding something, I never say good evening.
It's hard to say.
There's a... something about good evening?
What? Or...
Something?
What is it?
That's my ice cream.
I grabbed the red one.
No way.
You're doing great.
You're doing great today.
You've got common sense.
He's got common sense.
When you're talking to someone, you say hello first.
Okay, let's take a vote.
Please vote.Please.
Uh, which one of what?
What was that?
Good evening?
Oh, yeah.
Good evening.
I'm...
Surprise!
Surprise.
Good evening.
Good evening, I'm talking to you.
I'm feeling energetic.
Thank you very much for your vote.
They're all different.
It's true, they were very different.
It's like you asked me.
Oh!
Thanks for the good evening.
I'm surprised.
This will help me in my acting from now on.
I'm sure.
Yes, I'm absolutely sure I'm very good.
Now you know.
Good evening.
Then you know Ruri's good evening.
That's how you know Ruri's good evening.
You really got it.
Yes, thank you.Yes, thank you very much.
Let's see the results, shall we?
Yes, sir.
Number 2.
It's Arui.
What?
Wow!
That's great.
Oh, no.
You're lying.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. - Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
That's great.
There it is.
Right there.
Good evening.
Takashi!
It was like that, wasn't it?
Right?
Takashi.
Even after 30 years, I still feel like a maiden.
But you're still a girl.
It's awkward.
It's awkward for me, too.
Who is it?
So, thank you very much.So thank you all very much.
Thank you very much.
We'll get to the ending in no time.
Good morning.
Yes, it's Uguka no Yukari de Funa Showroom 195, and it's coming to an ending in no time at all!
Thank you very much.
Now I'm going to go to the announcement from Uka.
Okay.
Okay, here we go.
We are now holding a major first full album release!
November 15th, salt no good salt website!
This is a lot of traffic, isn't it?
Yes, it is!
Yes, it's me!
Yes, please come and play!
Yes, I will!
And November 19th is in Shibuya.
I made a mistake.
Oh, no...
Where is it not written?
Where?
I'm scared.
Asakusa wear, did you say it on the scaffold?
Oh, that's it.
That's it.
No, I wrote it down, like for real.
This way.
Oh, give it up, Shibuya. Oh, give it up, Shibuya.
I've never heard of it before.
Asakusa, right?
Yes, sir.
And the 23rd of November will be Kameido Clock
And November 26th, this is Shibuya
This is Shibuya
Magnet, by Shibuya 109
Yes, sir.
And December 16th, it's December already.
December 16th is Nagoya.
Yes, sir.
Past schedule
Yes
And December 17th is in Osaka
Yes, sir.
I knew it.
Yes.
And the future schedule for the canal.
Yes, sir.
November 12th, High Tension Fest 2023 at Shinjuku Blaze.
Yes, sir!
Tickets are now on sale to the general public, so please come and play!
And on November 18th, we will have KAWARA MATSURI on our 10th anniversary.
And Mark Shinjuku Loft
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir!
AndAnd then
And on the 3rd of December, the "Turoku Idol Festival" will arrive and be a success!
Yay!
Wait, it looks like Onigawara-san tweeted yesterday that there are still some tickets available for the KAWARA MATSURI!
Oh, so it's still possible!
Some tickets are still on sale, but I heard there are still some left.
Everyone can go!
Look forward to it!
I'm looking forward to it!
Oh, man!
I'm so excited!
And this is the one we've got for you... the ticket selection lottery is going on right now.
Yes!
And there's more!
A lot of these.
It's like vodka, isn't it?
This is a feeling of vodka.
Yes, on the 8th of December, Sayame Kawasawa's solo show will be held at Spelnova Kawasaki!
I'll be at Spelnova Kawasaki on December 8th.
Tickets are currently being selected for FC and will be available by tomorrow, so please come out and see me!
It's going to be great!
I'm so excited!
I want to go so much!
I've been thinking about it a lot, but...
I'm working hard on it.
Yes, yes.
Yes, I'm thinking about it.
Yes. Yes. Yes, sir.
Yes, sir.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you very much.
Well, I'm in charge. She is absolutely adorable, isn't she? I've been told that I can do whatever I want this time, so I'm in charge.
I can't wait to come. Yes, I showed them the design, but I'm not so sure if I can say that it's a chunk of the season anymore.
I hope to see you again in the future. I'm sure. I'm going to use that rail.
It's very different from Luka's usual style. It's just what I want to wear, so I think you'll like it a little bit.
But I'm sure it will be really cute. I think it's really cute. I think it's absolutely adorable. I hope you will like it.
And on January 21, we will be holding a live concert to unveil our new organization, New Chapter 7, at the Ebisu Liquid Room.
I am currently majoring in play guide.
Everyone is working hard in the lessons, so I hope you will all come to see us.
Please come and see us.
I hope you all can come and see us. So, we still have a lot of time left in our schedule, so please make time to come and see us.
Please make time to come and see me.
Please come and visit us in your own time. Now I would like to look at the final ranking.
I will be looking at the final ranking.Yes.
Fifth place, and Mr. Toboka.
Thank you very much.
And in fourth place, Ganryu Shimaotanii-san.
In third place, Takashi Ohkuri.
Thank you very much.
In second place, Risaku-san.
Third place, Daichi Sue.
Thank you very much.
The next broadcast will be on Wednesday, November 22nd at 7:00 p.m.
Yes, please register for the next broadcast.
To make sure you don't miss any broadcasts, please subscribe to our favorites by clicking on the heart mark.
Thank you very much.
I will also be doing some private broadcasts, so please give me a treat.
Please do.
Then, may we end?
Yes. That brings us to the end of the 195th episode of Ukka's "The Joyful Birth of a Boy.
See you next time on November 22nd.
That's all for now.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.